m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译 双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：依恋Elaine    Oktobertanz    伊森先生
翻译：Jacqueline    ntexplorer    minialicehuo
■
时间轴：大五朝台雨猪猪    逸苍漂云
校对：不辣的皮特厚       后期：Sung1219
医院
西班牙  卡纳利群岛
快点过来
-快过来  这边  -没事  我来
没关系  你来的时间刚刚好
It's okay, it's okay, you're just in time.
你会是个好父亲的  布莱恩
You're going to be a great father, Brian.
你为什么这么确定
What makes you so sure?
如果你不好好表现  我就弄死你
Because I'll be there to kick your ass if you ain't.
-快去吧  -快去吧
- Get in there. - Go.
布莱恩
Brian.
记住  你一旦踏入那扇门
Remember, the second you go through those doors,
一切都改变了
everything changes.
过去的生活不复存在了
Our old life is done.
去兜兜风吧
Let's go for a little ride.
出发吧
Here we go
这是我选择的人生
It's the life I chose
黑暗中响起枪声  我当没听到
Gunshots in the dark, one eye closed
我们的热火瞬间点燃黑夜
And we got it cooking like a one- eyed stove
亲吻姑娘的时候  我才会闭眼
You can catch me kissin' my girl with both eye closed
老子追求完美  谢谢各位关心
Perfecting my passion, thanks for asking
绝不放慢速度  宁愿粉身碎骨
Couldn't slow down so we had to crash it
你用吸管  老子用美金
You used plastic, we 'bout cash
前面的对手我们都要超越
I see some people ahead that we gon' pass
我从不害怕死亡
I never feared death or dying
只害怕无疾而终
I only fear never trying
我就是我
I am whatever I am
只有上帝才能对我指指点点
Only God can judge me, now
放手一搏
One shot
成败就在今晚
everything rides on tonight
即使三振
Even if I've got three strikes,
我也不会出局
I'ma go for it,
这个瞬间  属于我们
This moment, we own it
我不会轻易被人玩弄
And I'm not to be played with
因为这是危险游戏
Because it can get dangerous
看与我同行这些兄弟
See these people I ride with
这个瞬间  属于我们
This moment, we own it
与我闯荡的兄弟
And the same ones that I ride with
我们同生死共患难
be the same ones that I die with
出生入死
Put it all out on the line with
你抓不住我
if you looking for me
老子开着新车在众人之中
you can find with In the new car or in the crown whip
还有我的小妞  绝对火辣
My new broad, that's a fine chick
与我为伍的兄弟们
And the wonder squad, I'm down with
怎么样  你说怎样
What you say? Tell me what you say
努力奋斗  照顾小弟  每天如此
Working hard, reppin for my dogs, do this everyday,
坚守计划
Stuck to the plan,
不屈不挠  不做逃兵
always think that we would stand up, never ran
我们亲如一家  彼此永远忠诚
We the fam and loyalty never change up
白手起家  成就如此
Been down since day one, look at where we came from
有人评头论足  我就让你闭嘴
Jumpin out on anybody who try to say some one thing about it
你敢不服  包你折服
Got a problem, I got the same one
有钱我们就赚  有乐子我们玩
Money rolls, we fold Plently clubs we closed,
遵循信条
Follow the same code
永不反目  人不离车
Never turn our backs, our cars don't even lose control
放手一搏
One shot
成败就在今晚
everything rides on tonight
即使三振  我也不会出局
Even if I've got three strikes, I'ma go for it
这个瞬间  属于我们
This moment, we own it
没人敢玩弄我
And I'm not to be played with
因为这是危险游戏
Because it can get dangerous
看我同行的兄弟
See these people I ride with
这个瞬间  属于我们
This moment, we own it
莫斯科
-特别探员霍布斯  -莱利・希克斯
- Special Agent Hobbs? - Riley Hicks.
我看过你的简介  一流探员
I read your file. Top of your class at FLETC.
去过开罗  突尼斯
Cairo, Tunis.
阿富汗战争最年轻的地区安全警官
Youngest RSO ever in Afghanistan.
如果你有你简历里的一半好
Hell, if you're half as good as you are on paper,
咱们相处起来就没问题了
we're going to get along just fine.
俄国军方车队遭到袭击
A Russian military caravan attacked,
卫星元件被盗
satellite component stolen.
那车不知道从哪窜出来的
Cars just came out of nowhere.
六人入院  多车损毁
Six hospitalized, a dozen vehicles destroyed.
一共只用了90秒
All that in under 90 seconds, in and out.
绝对是一流的作案手法
This is world- class.
只有一个团队能完成
Job this good, there's only one crew in the world who could get this done.
这车怎么会跑那儿去
How the hell did that get up there?
他们抓住了一个罪犯
They caught one.
关在哪
Where?
国际刑警总部
我帮你争取了五分钟的审问时间
I got you five minutes with this guy.
两分钟就够
I only need two.
我要见你老板  肖在哪里
I want your boss. Where's Shaw?
我毛都不会告诉你的
I ain't telling you shit.
我就知道你会这么说
I was hoping you'd say that.
这样合法吗
Is that legal?
不
No.
但你想进去劝架吗
But are you going to go in there and tell him?
我有我的法律权利  你这混蛋
I've got rights, you asshole!
今天你什么都没有
Not today.
不要  不要
No, no!
-他开口了吗  -以后什么也说不了啦
- Well, is he talking? - Not anymore.
那房间有监听器
That room is bugged, Hobbs.
所以你得到的消息  国际刑警组织都知道
So, any information you just beat out of him, Interpol has now.
好极了  今天早上可以休息了  肖在伦敦
Great. Now they can take the morning off. Shaw's in London.
那我们去抓他吧
Let's go pick him up.
小姐  欧文・肖可不是想抓就抓的
Woman, you just don't pick up Owen Shaw like he's groceries.
对付他要以暴制暴
If you want to catch wolves, you need wolves.
捕猎开始了
Let's go hunting.
你这一亿就花在这上面吗
This is what 100 million buys?
找你一点都不难  托雷多
It wasn't that hard to find you, Toretto.
我又没在躲
I wasn't hiding.
退休的国际罪犯生活如何
How's the life of the retired international criminal?
我很喜欢这里  很平静
I like it here. It's quiet.
天气好得很
Nice weather,
也不用引渡
and no extradition.
警官  您有何贵干
So what are you doing here, cop?
上周二  有支训练有素的车队
Last Tuesday, a team of highly coordinated drivers
捣毁了一支俄国军方车队
took down an entire military convoy in Russia.
我可不在天冷的地方干活
I don't do cold weather.
我知道不是你
I know it wasn't you.
但你要帮我找出这支车队
But you're going to help me catch the team responsible.
你不需要这样
And you ain't gonna need that.
你不能抓他  霍布斯  他完全...
You can't touch him, Hobbs. You've got no powers...
我不想抓任何人
I'm not here to extradite anyone.
他会主动帮我的
See, he's going to come voluntarily.
事实上  应该说
As a matter of fact,
他得求我让他帮忙
he's going to beg me.
这是一周前的照片
This was taken a week ago.
门口见
I'll see you out front.
是拉蒂  对吧
It's Letty, isn't it?
这不可能
It's impossible.
如果照片上是我老公
If that was my husband,
如果有机会  不管多渺小
if there was a chance, no matter how small,
我都会奋力一搏
I would go.
我要知道一切  你手头一切信息
I'm going to need everything, all the info you got.
带来队伍  就告诉你
You'll get it when the team gets it.
没有队伍
No team.
就我一个人
This is going to have to be me alone.
你想得太简单了
It's not that simple.
这支车队
The crew we're after,
作案之后会马上消失
they hit like thunder and disappear like smoke.
你想自己上吗  完全没有机会
You go in alone, you won't ever touch them.
我追这伙人
I've been chasing this
追了四个大洲十二个国家
guy across four continents and 12 countries,
所以相信我  我最不想来的地方
and believe me, the last damn place I want to be right now
就是在你门口  忽悠你来帮忙
is on your front doorstep, selling Girl Scout cookies.
我需要你的帮助  唐
I need your help, Dom.
我需要你的队伍
I need your team.
女士们  把酒满上
Okay, ladies, bring it in.
我来祝个酒
Listen, I want to make a toast.
来吧
Come on.
我知道你们有人已经去过澳门了
Listen, I know a few of y'all have already been to Macau,
但跟我一起去
but you have never seen the town
你们才知道什么叫享受
till you've seen it through my eyes.
我有海景顶楼套房
We got a penthouse suite
会改变你们人生
with an ocean view that's going to change your life.
150英尺游艇  艇上有直升机
150- foot yacht with a helicopter pad...
应该说  我将带你们
Mmm- hmm. Safe to say,
见识一下极乐世界
you're about to have the time of your lives.
不  是你才对
No, you are.
干杯
Cheers.
快看  开着法拉利的高富帅
是啊  你以前可是罗宾汉  有钱大家花
你懂我意思的
钱改变了你
你说得对
钱的确改变了我
我意识到钱不是树上长出来的
是天上掉下来的
谢谢  看起来很好吃
粤语不错嘛
Nice!
这叫走遍世界都不怕
I'm a citizen of the world.
你想没想过安定下来
Ever thought about settling down?
一起开始一段新的人生
Starting a life together?
我们现在不就是这样吗
Aren't we doing that?
是吗
Are we?
放下你的枪
马上
哪位  唐
Hello? Dom?
我马上到
I'll be there.
哥们  把飞机调个头
Hey, my man, I need you to turn this plane around.
女士们  计划有变
All right, listen, ladies. There's been a little change of plans.
有临时状况
Something came up.
之前我跟你们说过的那家赌场
You know that casino I was telling you all about?
我有他们那儿
I got some vouchers
自助餐的代金券
to the buffet.
你喜欢这个吗
What do you think of this?
-他喜欢这个  -好吧
- He likes it. - All right.
是的
Yes.
还是这个
Or this?
真棒
Yes.
这才是我儿子  我们来试飞一下
That's my boy. All right, let's see how this thing flies.
在看吗
Are you watching?
快看谁来了  这不是唐叔叔吗
It's Uncle Dom. What do you know?
快招手  你好啊
Are you waving? What up?
好啊  杰克
Hey, Jack.
你好吗司机叔叔  你好唐叔叔
What's up, Uncle Dom? What's up, Uncle Dom?
很高兴见到你
You excited to see him?
你这是已经塞车给人家了吗
Are you already pushing imports on him?
哪有  爸爸不会逼你做任何事
You say, "Dad's not pushing anything."
他自己选的这辆车
He chose that car.
我们知道他是奥康纳家的儿子  但是
We know he's an O'Conner, but,
我给你带来了这个  杰克
I brought you something, Jack.
太棒了  他也是托雷多家的人
Yeah! He's also a Toretto.
现在还不着急做出选择呢  对吧
Luckily, he has a couple more years to decide, right?
人家能决定了  米娅
I think he decided, Mia.
他该睡午觉了
I think it's time for his nap.
来吧宝贝
Come on, baby. Okay.
拜拜啦
Say bye.
这感觉很奇怪吧
It's weird, huh?
什么奇怪
What's weird?
我现在  有了一切
We got everything.
甚至还有啤酒和烧烤
You know, down to the beer and the barbeque.
但是...
But it just...
但是感觉特别不像个家
I don't know, it just doesn't feel like home.
也许是因为
Maybe it's because, uh,
有些东西  直到失去
you don't realize how much you appreciate something
才会珍惜
until somebody takes it away.
我不知道
I don't know.
这地方变了许多
The place has probably changed so much,
你也许认不出来了
you wouldn't even recognize it anymore.
是啊
Yeah.
一切都变了
Everything's changed.
你怎么样  最近忙什么呢
So what's up with you? What's going on?
一周之前的照片
Taken a week ago.
外交安全局
Diplomatic Security Service.
霍布斯
Hobbs.
我以前也经常做这种事
You know, I used to do this shit all the time as a cop.
因为警察就是这样  扰乱你的生活
This is exactly what cops do. He's messing with your head.
拉蒂死了  唐
Letty's dead, Dom.
我必须要确定
I need to know for sure.
我和你一起去
Then I'm going with you.
你说过  过去的都过去了
You said you were going to leave this life behind.
我们都说过去的人生已经过去了
We both said that we were leaving the life behind.
他说得对
He's right.
我们就像亲人
We're family.
有难就要同当
If we got a problem, we deal with it together.
知道你们在外面互相扶持
And I'll feel safer knowing you're both out there,
我也会安心一点
watching each other's backs.
你们联手会更强大  一直都是这样
You're stronger together. You always were.
去找拉蒂吧
Now go get Letty.
带她回家
Bring her home.
伦敦
谢天谢地
Thank God!
终于有像样的装备了
Finally, some equipment I can work with.
好吗  小子
What up, boy?
比在里约的那堆垃圾强多了
This is way better than that trash in Rio.
强太多了
Way better.
你对他们有把握吗
You sure about these guys?
没有
Nope.
有里欧或桑托斯的消息吗
Has anybody heard from Leo or Santos?
最后一次有人在蒙特卡洛
Last time anyone saw them,
去赌场的路上见过他们
they were hitting up the casinos in Monte Carlo.
我以为那就是最后一单生意  布莱恩
I thought that was our last job, Brian.
这些装备谁来买单  纳税人吗
And who's paying for all this equipment? The taxpayers?
于是我们现在为绿巨人卖命吗  是这样吗
So now we work for The Hulk? That's what we're doing?
我怎么闻到婴儿霜的味道
Why do I smell baby oil?
你要是再不闭上你的臭嘴
If you keep running your piehole,
就会闻到屁股开花的味道
you're going to smell an ass- kicking.
霍布斯
All right, Hobbs,
世界上最优秀的队伍
you got the best crew in the world
就在这里
standing right in front of you.
给他们一个留下的理由
Give them a reason to stay.
我们的目标是欧文・肖
Our target is Owen Shaw.
前英国空军特勤队少校  黑色行动成员
Former major in the S.A.S., Spec- ops soldier.
他曾掌控喀布尔和波斯尼亚的英国空中机动处
He ran the UK's Mobility Division in Kabul and Basra.
真该死  这可不是盖的
Ah, damn. That Mobility unit's the truth.
这可是战争载具  他们是世界一流的
We're talking vehicular warfare. Best in the world.
-要点薯片吗  -他们可不是等闲之辈
- You got some chips? - Those guys don't mess around.
多年来  他们一直在欧洲作案
For years, they've been running jobs in Europe,
最近几桩生意
but it's their most recent jobs
让他们名声大噪
that graduated them to a whole new level.
他们袭击了三个特定目标
Three targets, highly specific.
一个是洲际弹道导弹的编程终端
The program terminal from an ICBM missile...
有零钱吗
Got a little change?
开什么玩笑
Seriously? You're a millionaire,
你这样的百万富翁还问别人要钱?
and you're still trying to ask for money?
这就是为什么你只是百万富翁
That's how you stay a millionaire.
这都是怎么回事
So what does this all mean?
最可能是肖的队伍
Well, our best guess is that Shaw's crew
正在建造某种暗影系统
is building a Nightshade device.
-什么系统  -一种科技炸弹
- Which is? - A tech bomb.
能使整个军方通讯电网
Designed to block an entire military communication grid
瘫痪24小时
for 24 hours.
战斗中哪怕只有一秒分神
If you blind a soldier for a single second
也能因此丧命
in the middle of a fight, he dies.
整个国家的通讯被切断24小时
If you blind a country for 24 hours,
所造成的伤亡根本无法想象
the loss of life is unthinkable.
在懂行的买家眼里这东西值几十亿
This could be worth billions to the right buyer.
有几十亿?
Billions?
我们干脆偷回来得了
Why don't we just steal that shit?
伙计
Hey, man.
哪个是一块钱
Which one of these things is a dollar?
这里写着...
It says something about...
我请客
It's on the house.
我需要你们帮我捉到肖
I want you to help me catch Shaw.
他还缺最后一件
He's only got one piece left that he needs,
我们要在他到手前阻止他
and I intend to stop him before he gets it.
我知道你们像亲人一样
Now, I know you guys are a family.
现在我就给你们一个机会
So I'm offering you a chance right now
让这个家庭再次团圆
to make that family whole again.
你想让我们再次团圆吗
You want to make this family whole again?
带我们找拉蒂  我们会捉住肖
Get us to Letty, we'll get you Shaw,
之前的案底一笔勾销
full pardons all the way around.
这个我保证不了
I can't promise you that.
你可以
Yes, you can.
这就是条件
That's the deal.
接不接受随你
Take it or leave it.
你们捉到肖
You get me Shaw,
我就给你们豁免
and I'll get your pardons.
你们都听到了
You heard him.
但这次不一样
But this is different.
我们不是对付条子
We're not dealing with cops,
也不是对付毒贩
we're not dealing with drug dealers.
根本不是一个级别
This is a whole different level.
这活有报酬吧
We're getting paid, right?
把衣服掀起来
Lift your shirt.
国际刑警在莫斯科逮到一个肖的手下
Interpol picked up one of Shaw's guys in Moscow.
我对他进行了心理辅导
I went in, had a little therapy session with him.
他供出了肖的藏身之处
He gave up Shaw's hideout.
那我们为什么不行动
Then why aren't we down there now?
人家没邀请我们
Well, we weren't invited.
霍布斯  诱饵已经放回去了
Hobbs, they're sending in your punching bag.
他带着通讯设备
He's wired.
他们行动之前先确定里面那个是不是肖
He's going to give a positive ID on Shaw before they move in.
条子就这么把你放了?
So, the cops just let you go, huh?
别担心  我什么都没说
Don't worry, I didn't give them shit.
我不是担心
Oh, I'm not worried.
好了
Okay,
帮我启动它
turn it over for me.
行了
God, it's amazing.
最简单的东西也能引发最大的问题
The simplest things can cause the biggest problems.
但好消息是  把坏的部分换掉
Good news is, if you swap out a bad part,
一切还是完美无瑕
everything runs smooth as silk again.
听着  肖
Look, Shaw.
等等
Wait, Shaw! Shaw!
肖
Shaw!
语音匹配  欧文・肖
确认是肖无误  让他们行动吧
I just got confirmation on Shaw. They're going in.
等等  慢着  慢着
Wait, wait, hold up...
警用扫描设备显示
Police scanners are saying
国际刑警总部遭侵入
alarms are going off at Interpol headquarters.
该死
Shit.
他引开我们  好去对付国际刑警
He brought us here so he could take down Interpol.
这一切都是个陷阱
This whole thing's a set-up.
-布莱恩  你带队走  -你呢
- Brian, take the team. - What about you?
霍布斯和我等着肖
Hobbs and I will wait for Shaw.
肖能带我们找到拉蒂
Shaw leads to Letty.
快出来  王八蛋
Come on, you son of a bitch.
这是什么
What's this?
上次干活的报酬
It's your share from the last job.
你也是一份子  奥克斯
You're part of the team, Oakes.
干了活当然有报酬
You do your job, you get paid.
里面还有点额外奖励
There's a little extra in there for you.
就当是预支吧
Consider it an advance.
预支什么
For what?
预支下次任务的报酬
The next job, of course.
什么任务
Which job?
我们现在做的这个
The one we're working right now.
汉  离国际刑警总部还有多远
Han, how far are we from Interpol?
还有两个街口
Twelve blocks away.
伙计们  这里跟座鬼城一样
You guys, it's a ghost town over here.
肖把所有条子都引到那边去了
Shaw must have pulled all the cops to him.
游戏该结束了  干掉他们
All right, y'all, we're in this shit, so let's go get it.
跟你赛车很愉快  伙计
It's been fun running with you, mate.
把包扔掉
Stop! Drop the bag!
-他来了  -收到
- There he is. - On it.
托雷多  在你前面  别跟丢了
Toretto, it's on you. Straight ahead, don't lose him.
绝对不会
Ain't gonna happen.
抱歉  伙计们
Sorry about that, boys.
国际刑警总部就在前面了
Interpol, straight ahead.
兄弟们  有贵客上门了
Let's go, guys. We've got company.
行动  兄弟们
Let's go, boys.
我们上
Get in! Let's go!
我们得行动  快
Hey! We got to move. Now!
肖  有三辆车尾随我们
Shaw, we have three cars tailing us.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
准备好芯片干扰  快点
我来应付这辆路虎
Guys, I got the Rover.
好  那我来应付...
Okay, I got...
这个叫不上名的鬼东西
Whatever the hell that thing is.
那是什么  冰球吗
What is that, a hockey puck?
打中了
一号芯片已就绪
该死
Oh! Shit!
最后一台芯片就位
没用  没用
正在接近目标位置
Approaching rendezvous point.
唐  泰吉和罗曼被撞翻了  你在哪
Dom! Tej and Roman are out! Where you at?
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you!
快到了  我要放手一搏
Stay on track. I'm taking the contingency.
大伙  我盯住肖了  他刚刚左转
Boys, I got eyes on Shaw. He just made a left.
-我去右边  -托雷多  左转
- I got right. - Toretto, make that left!
玮
我需要你的帮助
没问题
No problem.
拉蒂
Letty.
你来驾驶
Take the wheel.
拉蒂
Letty.
真是疯了
This is crazy.
我们又不是在巴西
We are not in Brazil.
你们居然玩起了空中飞车?
So, now we got cars flying in the air?
还是在拍007吗  我们不能这样做
On some 007- type shit? This is not what we do!
伙计  你该去做心理检查了
Man, you really got to check that emotion.
你的公鸭嗓都变成狗狗音了
Your voice just went from Shaggy to Scooby- Doo.
"我们不能...汪汪汪"
"This is not what we..."
当一个女人冲你开枪时
See, man, when a woman starts shooting at you,
你就该夹起尾巴开溜
that's a clear sign to back the fuck off!
我们不能再这样下去了
We need to get the hell out of Dodge!
如果打中我脑门怎么办  伙计
That could have been my forehead, man.
不会
No.
你脑门比这大多了
That's not as big as your forehead.
米娅
Mia.
是拉蒂没错
Uh, It's definitely Letty.
但情况很复杂
But it's, uh.. It's complicated.
拉蒂还活着
Letty's alive.
这才是最重要的
That's all that matters.
我们都支持她  布莱恩
We have her back, Brian.
帮我给杰克一个晚安吻吧
Well, do me a favor and give Jack a kiss goodnight for me.
-一定要平安  -我爱你  米娅
- Be safe. - I love you, Mia.
她看清楚是你了吗
She definitely saw it was you?
她直盯着我  布莱恩
She looked dead at me, Brian.
也许我们认识的拉蒂已经消失了  唐
Maybe the Letty we once knew is gone, Dom.
就算她还活着  也不是原来的她了
Even though she's alive, maybe she's gone.
我们不能跟亲人反目
You don't turn your back on family.
即使他们这样做了
Even when they do.
-艾维  -在
- Ivory. - Yo.
这辆车需要修理
It's going to need some repairs.
没问题  甜心
No problem, treacle.
你没事吧
Are you good?
没事
Yeah.
好了  全体注意
Okay, listen up.
这次跟霍布斯以往那些喽不一样
That was a very different breed from Hobbs' usual wannabe warriors.
来看看他们是什么来头  都有什么本事
We need to learn who these people are, what they're made of.
玮
Vegh?
奥康纳  帕克
O'Conner, Parker,
皮尔斯  托雷多
Pearce, Toretto
加上其他队员
and the rest of the team.
这群人都是普通罪犯而已
These guys are common criminals.
就是这群普通罪犯
Tonight these common criminals were seconds away
差点将我们打败
from taking us down.
给他们应有的尊重  不然骄兵必败
Show them the respect they deserve, or it weakens us.
你该看看这个
You might want to see this.
能想起什么来吗
Ring any bells?
是的
Yeah.
这就是我打伤的那个人
That's the guy I shot.
照片里你挺开心的
You look happy.
我不记得他了
I don't remember him.
简直胡说八道
That's bullshit.
我们有麻烦了  伙计们
We got a problem, guys.
跟她合影的那个男人差点就把你拉下马
We got a picture of her with the guy who almost took you out.
克劳斯  你不是肌肉男吗
Klaus, aren't you team muscle?
别逼我不讲情面  把你变成娘炮
Don't make me go over there and make you team pussy.
她不记得他了
She doesn't remember him.
光有名字和档案还不够
Names and records aren't enough.
我需要私人信息
I want personal information.
生活琐事  他们的所思所想
Get into their lives, into their minds.
一旦找到弱点  就能将他们一举击溃
Find their weaknesses, and we will exploit them.
好极了
Mmm- hmm. Yeah, right.
这也太疯狂了  伙计
This is crazy, man.
你又在嘟囔什么
What are you talking about now?
我在这里查看这些图片
I'm sitting here looking at these images,
就好象要追捕邪恶版本的自己一样
it's like we're hunting our evil twins.
看看这个小黑哥  他真帅
Look at this black dude right here, he's handsome.
简直是我的影子
Clearly, that's me.
还有白版霍布斯  这是汉
We got a white Hobbs. This is Han.
这个是泰吉  还带着非洲小帽
Tej, it's an African in a beanie.
就像你的迷你版本
That's like your Mini- Me, man.
布莱恩
And Brian!
你什么时候拍的这写真
When did you do this photo shoot?
我逗逗你而已
I'm just playing, man.
你是这里最美的金发妞
You know you're the prettiest blonde around here.
都给我精神点  两件事要说
All right, lock it up. We got two things.
第一
First off,
这城市是罪犯的噩梦
this is the worst damn city in the world to commit a crime.
每个街角都有监控摄像头
They got cameras on every street corner.
这是闭路电视带子
I got video footage from CCTV of the raid.
看看我们能不能发现什么
Let's track that, see where it leads us.
第二
And secondly,
我们知道了肖的团伙抢了什么
we just got confirmation on what Shaw's crew grabbed from Interpol.
他们黑了一个数据库
They ripped off the database
里面有他们要的东西存放的地点
of every location that houses the final component that they need.
在哪里
So where are they at?
在欧洲一共有20多个
There are over two dozen of them around Europe.
这列表有效期只有96小时
But the list is only good for 96 hours.
这意味着  不管他们目标是什么
Which means, wherever Shaw's crew is going to hit next,
他们一定在四天内动手
it's going to happen within the next four days.
他们有目标了  我们也一样
They got a window, and so do we.
-动手吧  -霍布斯说的对
- We gotta move. - Hobbs is right.
我们来分析一下
So let's break this down.
大干一场吧  我们有什么情报
You met them. What do we know?
他们一定在用自己订制的引擎
We know they have to be running custom engines.
你也听到那车换档的声音了
You heard that flip car going through those gears.
顺序式变速箱
Sequential transmission.
那引擎听起来可不一般
That didn't sound like a normal engine.
柴油涡轮增压引擎
That was a turbo diesel.
它听起来是从勒芒[法国城市]来的
It sounded like something you hear at Le Mans.
就算被撞
Did you see it take all those hits
那车也能保持平稳
and still stay flat in the corners?
没错  液压稳定装置
Yeah, hydraulics.
还有磁悬浮悬挂
Or magnetic suspension.
想想有谁能接触到那些零件
Who not only has access to the components,
还能改造它们
but can fabricate something like that?
伦敦有很多店可以
Maybe a handful of shops in London.
普通的店可不敢做
Regular tuner shops aren't going to cut it on this one.
我们得深挖一下线索
We're going to have to dig deeper than that.
汉  吉赛尔和罗曼  你们上
Han, Gisele, Roman, you're up.
我们只要找到造那辆车的人
We find the guy who made that car,
就能找到肖
we find Shaw.
走吧
Let's go.
-我也来帮忙  -没问题
- I'll help. - Roger that.
泰吉
Tej,
我们需要不带芯片的车子
we're gonna need cars without computer chips that can be overridden.
必须快到极致
Make sure they're fast.
看我的吧
I got this.
已经在办了  唐
I'm already on it, Dom.
我联系了皇家海军和外交安全局
I've contacted R&D at DSS.
霍布斯
Hobbs.
我说了就看我的吧
I said I got this.
越来越有趣了
This should be interesting.
伙计  你得放轻松点
Man, you really got to loosen up.
就弄些工厂出的普通货色
You can't just throw a bunch
这些行家可不会满意
of factory- line Beemers at people and expect...
这可是一辆牛车啊
Hey. That car is a hell of a car.
双涡轮增压V8引擎
You're talking about twin- turbo V8,
足有560匹马力呢
spitting out 560 ponies, son.
做了不少功课啊  真替你感到骄傲
He reads the brochure. I'm proud.
但只有订制的车子才最牛
But with cars, you have to customize.
在你和车之间
It's all between you and the car you build.
必须有一种联系  一种承诺
It's a bond, it's a commitment.
听起来和结婚没两样
It sounds like a marriage.
但你和车子分手时
Yeah, but with cars, when you trade up,
它们不会分你一半财产
they don't take half your shit.
老天爷
Jesus.
看这价位  车子肯定是黄金打造
With price tags like this, these cars better be made out of gold.
你不会在考虑偷这些车吧  帕克
You ain't thinking about stealing these cars, are you, Parker?
帮厨的入口在后面
Kitchen help entrance is towards the back.
你说什么
Come again?
无意冒犯
I don't mean any offense, gentlemen,
不过你们可买不起这些车
but you couldn't possibly afford the cars in this auction.
全身没带点珠宝  也没点贵族气息
Substantial lack of gaudy jewelry, no entourage, no honeys.
明显  你也不是个舞伴
Clearly you're not a "Baller."
还有你
And you.
不管是鞋子衬衣还是裤子
Hmm. Shoes, shirt, trousers.
都是休闲的
Functional.
身姿又很僵硬
And your posture, too rigid, no swagger.
估计是个5万块钱一年的大兵哥
My guess is military. Take home of 50,000 a year.
我说的可是美元
That's U.S.
肯定不够你来这儿花销了
Which is not enough to be playing here.
你们要不是帮厨
So, if you're not kitchen help,
那肯定是来错地方了
then you must be in the wrong place.
不过呢  喝完这杯再走人吧
But please, do finish your champagne.
得给他点教训才行
Oh, he needs to be taught a lesson.
我说过了  你不可以偷这些车
Like I said, you ain't stealing these cars.
我知道啦
I got this.
到了  这就是列表上的5号
All right, this is number five on our list.
我的老天爷
Holy shit.
那伙计要猎杀什么啊  大白鲸吗
What's the dude plan on hunting? Moby Dick?
是他没错了
That must be our guy.
你们准备怎么下手
So, how do you all want to play this?
我和汉就能搞定
Han and I got this.
我们俩下去  让我来搞定一切
We go in tight, you let me do all the talking,
你们站后面看就行了
and you all have my back on it.
你俩老爷们忘了一件事
There's one thing you boys are forgetting.
他终归是个男人
He's a man.
我们上
Let's go.
他是个男人
"He's a man"?
她总是这么说
You know, she always says that.
你手里的是5.45乘18口径
What you're looking at is a 5.45
FMJ全金属弹头子弹
by 18 FMJ spitzer bullet.
是手枪专用子弹  PSM手枪
It's specific to one handgun, the PSM.
事实上  私持手枪在英国是违法的
Given that handguns are illegal in the United Kingdom,
只有少数人可以持有那样的枪械
there's very few people that have access to that firearm.
既然是这样
So if somebody wanted to, say,
追查枪的来源
track down where it came from,
不会太困难
it wouldn't be too hard.
当警察那么久  老习惯还是改不了
I was a cop for a lot of years. Some habits die hard.
典当铺
A pawn shop.
谁介绍你们来的
Who sent you?
说吧  美人儿
Come on, ladies!
一般像你俩这种美人儿来我这
Two hot girls like you don't wander into this neighborhood
我都会先打个电话给你们妈咪的
unless l've called the escort service.
今天不打电话竟然自动上门了
And l haven't, yet, today.
她们行吗  我可不看好
I don't know, man. That was disrespectful.
我也不喜欢她的语气
And I don't like the way she said it,
他终归是个男人
like, "He's a man."
他是个男人  那我们算什么
"He's a man"? So, what are we?
算了  她只是为了任务
Come on, she's just doing her job.
什么为了任务
"Doing her job."
我算看明白了
I see what's going on.
看明白什么
See what?
你八成爱上她了吧
You got the little stardust in your eyes, eh?
爱情鸟在脑袋周围转圈
Little birds floating around a little bit.
合伙做任务不够  你还想纳她入后宫
Uh, you don't want to lease this model. You want to buy.
你可以闭嘴了
Can you please stop talking?
你坠入爱河啦  看看你的样子
No, no, you're in love! Look at you!
快闭嘴吧
Just stop.
有没有制定泡妞计划  来个美妙约会
You got special plans? Big day?
把我们都请来
You're going to invite us all out?
你可得买颗大点的钻石
Better make sure you get her a big rock, man,
她可没那么容易被驯服
'cause she doesn't look like she'll be that easily impressed.
要是钻石不大
And if it's not a big rock,
那玩意儿大也行呀
you better be big somewhere else.
你懂的
You know what I'm talking about.
所以你马子才带那么多首饰是吧
That's why all your girlfriends wear so much bling, huh?
我们需要点情报
We're looking for information.
你们需要情报? 有关什么的
You're looking for information? About what?
当然是有关车子的
Information about cars.
尤其是你最近设计的两辆
In particular, two you designed recently.
道奇公羊  低底盘  车颈框架
Ramp cars. Low slung, skeletal frames.
我们对买那些车的人很感兴趣
We'd be very interested to find the man who bought those.
我为什么要帮你们
Why should I help you?
因为我们真诚相求了
Because we're asking you nicely.
就因为真诚相求吗
Because you're asking me nicely?
那就看你有什么特殊的本事了
What can you offer that I can't get from a thousand other girls?
住手  住手啊
Stop! Stop!
你看上去挺能抗
You look like a man who likes it rough.
我的这位朋友可以给你最剧烈的疼痛
My friend here can give you heights of pain
我敢肯定你以前从未体验过
you've never experienced before.
想做交易了吗
Do we have a deal?
我做  我做
Deal! Deal! Deal!
我收回刚才的话
I take it back.
我也爱这小妞
Me likey.
好了  好了  停
Stop, stop, stop.
这就是你的方法吗  把它们全买下来
So this is how you "Got this"? By buying all of his cars?
钱都烂在银行的话
What good is having millions of dollars in the bank
人生就没有意义了
if you don't spend any of it?
别担心  看我的
But don't worry about that. Watch this.
帕克先生  请允许我再一次表达谢意
Mr. Parker, again, can I just express our gratitude
非常感谢您带来的生意
and say how much we appreciate your business.
如果您还有任何需要  请尽管提出要求
If there's ever anything else you need, you just have to ask.
任何需要吗
Anything?
既然你这么说了
Now that you mention it, my swagger- less friend here,
我的朋友很中意你的衬衫
he really likes that shirt you have on.
身上这件吗
Uh, this shirt?
就是那件
That shirt.
这么小他恐怕穿不下吧
I'm not entirely sure that this shirt would fit your friend.
我穿的下
It will fit.
他需要一件不那么
He needs a shirt that's a little less...
休闲的衬衫
Functional.
没错  太休闲了
That's it, functional.
好吧
Okay.
-我来拿着  -谢谢
- I'll hold that. - Thank you.
赶紧的  时间就是金钱
Come on, man, time is money.
我正尽力呢
Yes, doing my best.
靠  老兄你该褪褪毛了吧
Damn, you need some hedge clippers for that shit.
这下您满意了吧
Well, if that will be all...
裤子也脱了
And the pants, too.
当然了
Right.
把那手表也那来吧
While you're at it, let me get that watch.
我喜欢那块表
I like that watch.
这条是您的
This is for you.
-这块是您的  -谢谢
- And this is for you. - Thank you.
祝愉快  谢谢
Good day, gentlemen. Thank you.
我把资料放这里了
So I, um, I got the information in here.
能问一下你们找肖做什么吗
May I ask why you're looking for Shaw?
他拿了我们的东西
He took something of ours.
我们得和他谈谈
We'd like to talk to him about it.
看看我们能找到什么吧
Let's see what we've got.
小子  你想怎样
All right. What do you want?
我们要找一把俄罗斯的枪
They say if someone's looking for a Russian gun,
大家说可以找你
you're the man to see.
是这样没错
Oh, they do, do they?
找麻烦吗  伙计
What do you want, mate?
想死就进来
That might be a bad idea.
-我在找这个的主人  -我不知道
- I'm looking for the owner of this. - I don't know.
看看仔细再说
Take a closer look.
大概一星期前
About a week ago, a girl came in,
一个女孩来买走了所有东西
bought guns, ammo, everything I had.
一个女孩吗
A girl?
她长什么样
What did she look like?
瘦脸颊  深色头发
Tough chick, dark hair.
身材消瘦
Mean streak.
据说是个赛车手
Word is she's a street racer.
去哪能找到她
Where can we find her?
我怎么知道  我看起来像赛车手吗
How do I know? Do I look like a racer?
你确实不像
No. You don't.
伙计们保重
Take care, guys.
该死
Oh, shit.
抱歉了女士们
Sorry, girls.
快走
Let's go!
坚持住
Hold on.
保持清醒
Stay with me. Stay with me.
告诉我如何找到肖
Tell me where to find Shaw,
我会让他付出代价
and I'll make him pay for this.
布拉加
Braga...
喂  叫你呢
Hey, you!
站住别动
Stop right there!
-上  -不  还是你上
- Go! - No! You go!
这事谁也不能知道
No one needs to know about this.
谁都不行
No one.
我们失去了艾维
We lost Ivory.
他死了
He's gone.
谢了
Thanks.
你就说这些吗
That's it?
如果艾维死了  那说明他犯了个错
If Ivory's dead, he made a mistake.
一旦犯了错误  就要付出代价
If you make a mistake, you pay the price.
你真是说得一口好悼词  肖
That's a great eulogy, Shaw.
我们下次再外出行动时
Are you going to give the same speech
你也打算这么说吗
for the rest of us when we go out?
我没想到你会这么多愁善感
You're the last one I'd have pegged to be sentimental.
我喜欢你  拉蒂
I like you, Letty.
甚至呆在你身边都让我觉得很温暖
I dare say I even feel a certain warmth towards you.
当我在医院
When I found you in the hospital,
发现失去记忆的你时
and you couldn't remember anything,
我告诉自己
I said to myself,
这个女孩天赋异禀
"This girl has a gift.
她就像一张白纸
"She's a blank page."
这激起了我对你的保护欲
And that made me feel somewhat protective toward you.
如果你出了什么事
If something happened to you, for instance,
我会难以承受
I think I might find that slightly harder to bear.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is,
我不想看到你
I would hate to see you
犯那种错误
make a mistake.
我去透透气
I'm going to get some air.
-怎么了  -我们见过唐的女友了
- What the hell happened? - We met Dom's girlfriend.
她挺可爱的
She's lovely.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you all right? - Yeah.
伙计们  查看监控系统有什么进展吗
Tej, what have you got? Footage, CCTV? Talk to me.
全部的监控录像我都看过了
I just went through all of it.
你敢信吗
Believe it or not,
肖的团队出现过的地方摄像头都坏了
everywhere Shaw's team is, the cameras are down.
是巧合吗
That's a hell of a coincidence.
看来我们得去查看一下监控中心  走吧
All right, we're going to pay CCTV a little visit. Let's roll.
这是什么
What is that?
那是给你带回来的新玩意
That is a new toy for you.
到底发生了什么
So, what happened?
肖的人突然出现  拿着枪乱扫
Shaw's goons showed up and started shooting up the place.
但我们拿到了好东西
But we got something big.
-是什么  -布拉加
- What? - Braga.
他和肖是合作关系
He's working with Shaw.
你这话是什么意思
What are you talking about?
她说的对  那人手机上的交易支付记录
It's true. That phone's filled with coded payment transactions
都直指布拉加的贩毒集团
that lead straight to Braga's cartel.
那个布拉加是谁
Who the hell is Braga?
他是墨西哥最大的毒枭之一
He ran one of the biggest cartels in Mexico.
我曾经为他卖过命
And my old boss.
我们也曾用他们那种密码
We used codes just like that
把钱转移出国
to move money out of the country.
这能说的通
It all makes sense.
拉蒂曾被布拉加追杀  如今是肖的手下
Braga was running Letty, now he's working with Shaw.
布拉加和肖就是这么认识的
It would explain how the two of them met.
你们信息很全面
Okay, so you all know all this information about him,
但我们要怎么找到他
where do we find him?
他在洛杉矶蹲监狱呢
He's sitting in a prison in Los Angeles.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
是布莱恩把他关进去的
Brian put him there.
他现在就是我们的突破口
All right, so this is the break we were looking for.
既然他们在合作
If the two of them were working together,
那布拉加一定知道肖的企图
Braga will know what Shaw's up to.
我去拜访他一下
I'm going to pay him a visit.
你别开玩笑了
Are you serious right now?
用脑子好好想想你刚刚说的话
Think about what you're saying.
你现在是通缉犯  布莱恩
You're wanted, Brian.
你只要一踏上美国就会被判刑
The moment you step foot off that plane, it's a wrap.
你就回不来了
You're not coming back.
别说回不来了  你怎样才能进入美国
"Coming back"? How are you going to get in the country?
这个不是问题
Let me worry about that.
这是我的责任
This is on me.
是我把布拉加抓进去的
I'm the one that served her up to Braga.
所以我要把这事办好
I'm the one that gets to make it right.
我一定会成功的
Let me make it right.
注意安全
Be careful.
他现在可以见你了  这边请
He's ready to see you now. Right this way.
谢谢你能见我们
Thank you for seeing us.
这不会耽搁你太长时间
I won't take up much of your time.
我的手下今天早些时候遭到攻击
My men were attacked earlier today.
我要查看一下在滑铁卢车站内
I'm going to need to see all cameras
和其周边的监控录像
in and around Waterloo station.
谁来告诉这位美国队长这是需要被批准的
Will somebody tell Captain America here that requires clearance?
特里
Terry,
把58至62号摄像机早些的录像调出来
bring up cameras 58 through 62, earlier today.
这些摄像机由于维修今晨全部关闭了
They've been down for maintenance all morning.
抱歉了
Sorry.
好吧  那算了  感谢你的帮助
Okay. Well, we appreciate your help. Thank you.
我发现了一个十分有趣的事
You know what I find very interesting
国际刑警总部最近也发生了攻击事件
is Interpol was attacked recently as well.
那里的摄像机也坏了  什么都没拍到
Those cameras were down, too. Didn't catch a thing.
什么也没有
Nothing.
也就是说  要么是
Now, that means either
你们的维修时间
your maintenance schedule lines up
和案件出奇的同步
perfectly with their escape route
要么就是你们这有内奸
or it's someone here that's working with them.
不过这事也太扯了
And that's just ridiculous.
因为说到你们这有内奸的话
Because there ain't no way in hell
那是不可能的
anybody here would be working for them.
更不会是你  对吧
Particularly you, ain't that right?
不  这太扯了
No, no, that's ridiculous.
是啊  的确很扯
That is ridiculous.
我要获取你的所有监控信号
I'm going to need direct access to your live feed
要全市范围的
citywide.
我强烈建议你这次
And I also strongly suggest that you put a hold on any more
暂停你们的维修工作
"Maintenance."
没问题
Yeah, of course.
十分感谢你的帮助
We appreciate your help. Thank you so much.
洛杉矶
看啊看啊
Well, well, well.
你穿橘色很适合啊
The orange in that really makes your eyes pop.
谢了  伙计们
Thanks, fellas.
和我说说  奥康纳
Tell me something, O'Conner,
你满世界逃窜
how is it you keep running around the world,
不断寻找法律的漏洞  可是
breaking every law known to man,
为什么我现在把你抓住了呢
and yet here I am, putting my job on the line for you?
如果我把抓住肖
You'll feel a lot better
归功于你怎么样
once you get the credit for taking down Shaw.
抓住你我已经很满意了
Oh, I'm tempted to settle for you.
你知道吗  斯塔夏克
Well, you know what they say, Stasiak,
你要是想抓个大人物
if you want the career- changing big fish,
你就该懂得
you got to be willing to put on the big boy panties
舍不得孩子套不着狼的道理
and sail out to the deep water.
你就是个混蛋
You're an asshole, you know that?
我想死你了伙计  真的
I missed you, too, man. I really missed you.
我给你做的假身份
I got you admitted
能让你做你该做的事
into Victorville to do whatever you got to do.
24小时拘留
It's a 24- hour hold.
明天9点你前必须逃出去
You need to be out of there by 9:00 a.M.
你的指纹
That's when Forensics will run
会被输入国家指纹库
your fingerprints through the national database.
指纹库会开始匹配你的指纹
That program will match you
但当他们发现你的真实身份后
and when they find out who you really are,
连我都没法把你救出来了
I won't be able to get you back out.
监狱生活可是水深火热
We're talking life in prison.
你孩子很可爱
Cute kid.
布拉加被关在监狱D-3区
So, I found out Braga's being held in cell block D3.
是单独的房间
That's solitary.
我只能把你安排在普通狱区
I only had enough juice to get you in Gen Pop.
所以你得有所行动让他注意到你
So you're going to have to do something to get his attention.
抱歉了伙计
Sorry about this, man.
什么抱歉
Sorry about what?
又来
Again?
看现场直播咯
Big Brother's about to go live.
在伦敦
Damn, you can't flick a
想偷偷摸摸干点事情还真难
booger in London without somebody noticing.
别乱碰  那可不是用来玩的
Hey! Don't touch that. That's nothing to play with, man.
怎么了啊
What's the problem?
那可是高张量钛电缆做的
That's high- tensile titanium cable.
那是什么啊
What does that mean?
是打地基和撑桥梁的材料
That's what they use to anchor buildings and hold up bridges,
不懂别乱碰
stuff you know nothing about!
他们做的版本 只能说是过得去
See, now, their version, it works cool,
我的可是大师手笔
but mine, masterpiece.
你看我把齿轮安到发动机后面去了
See, I reversed the gears, torqued the motor
还在后面加上了这个罐子
and added this tank to the back.
那就让我更想玩一把了
That makes it even sweeter.
这可是真枪实弹
It does.
不是模型
It's not dummy- proof.
我知道怎么操作大型枪支  放松点
Man, I've been known to handle big guns. Relax.
这个你可不会用
You've been known to handle that big- ass head.
唐  我做了点调查  询问了下周边情况
Dom, I did some checking, asked around,
找到了一处可以赛车的地方
got the location of a street race tonight.
四辆雪弗兰美式超跑
Four speed Camaro SS big block.
帅吧
You like it?
颜色真帅
Nice color.
布莱恩・奥康纳
Brian O'Conner.
真是巧遇啊
That was quite an entrance.
你抓了怎么多人进来
You put a lot of these men in here.
怎么  你觉得没人能认出你来吗
What? You didn't think one would recognize you?
大家可都记着你呢
I've kept tabs on you, you know.
你在外面玩的很开心啊
You've been having a lot of fun out there.
在里约热内卢时你变成了个坏警察
Good cop gone bad, Rio de Janeiro.
犯罪的感觉是不是很爽
It's exciting when you go criminal, isn't it?
你要是早点变成坏警察就可以为我干事了
Too bad you didn't do it earlier, you could have worked for me.
就像拉蒂・奥蒂斯一样是吗
Like Letty Ortiz?
告诉我点她的事  因为我亲手埋葬了她
So tell me something, because I buried her.
是吗
Yeah? You did?
我怎么知道你埋了什么
You buried something, I couldn't tell you who or what it was.
我知道她为肖工作
I know she's running with Owen Shaw.
布莱恩你还是有颗警察心啊
Still playing cop, huh?
就凭你的等级还不配知道这些
Trust me, this is way above your pay grade.
别嘲笑我了
Humor me, please.
反正你也是行尸走肉了  告诉你也无妨
Well, you're a dead man walking, what does it matter?
我替肖打理一切事物
I ran everything for Shaw.
毒品  枪支  金钱  女人
Drugs, guns, money, women.
在我眼光狭隘时他教会我把目光放远
He taught me to think global when I was just local.
我变富了
He made me a wealthy man.
不仅他的毒品集团为我工作
And this guy didn't just have the cartels working for him.
中情局  缉毒局  他控制着所有人
He had the CIA, DEA, everyone in his pocket.
他比他们更早掌握第一手消息
He knew what was going to happen before they did.
事实上他早就知道乳臭未干的FBI探员
In fact, he even knew when some wet- behind- the- ears FBI agent
打算把卧底安排进我的毒品集团的事
decided to put some informant in my cartel.
你让拉蒂做卧底结果害死了她
The minute you put Letty undercover, she was dead, bro.
她活下来了
But she survived.
这女孩命真硬
That girl is one tough bitch.
肖两天后在医院找到她
Shaw found her in a hospital two days later.
打算杀了她
He went to finish the job.
但他为什么没杀她
And he didn't kill her. Why?
她失忆了
She had no memory.
简直太完美了
Perfect girl, huh?
你该庆幸我们之间有道门隔着
You're lucky this door's between us.
你得为拉蒂的事负责
What happened to Letty is on your head.
看着我  看着我
Look at me! Look at me.
你不会杀我的
You won't do it.
肖到底有什么企图
What is Shaw up to?
他对你的行动了如指掌
How do you think he knows your next move before you make it?
他一直监视着你
He's got eyes on you.
想想吧
Think about it.
除非他想见你
The only way you get close to Shaw
否则你无法接近他
is if he wants you there.
你胆子还真大
You've got some serious balls, man.
都这么说
I've been told.
你很幸运我上次没射中你
You know, you're lucky I missed my shot.
我觉得你打得挺准
I think you hit your mark.
是吗
Really?
你到底想干嘛
What is it with you?
不想活了还是怎样
Do you got a death wish or something?
没什么大不了的
If that's what it takes.
我就是想赛一局
I just want to race.
你有可能会输掉你的车
You might lose your car.
来赛一局吧
Let's do it.
你死定了
Your funeral.
还记得吗  要么赛车要么死
Ride or die, remember?
都听好了
Listen up!
我们在这里追寻我们心之所向
Out here, we're used to getting what we want.
这里是伦敦  伙计们
This is London, baby.
但记住了
But remember,
别轻易上钩
don't bite the bait.
你们准备好了吗
Are you ready?
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Ready.
稳住
Steady.
开始
Go!
简直是重温以前的时光啊
Just like old times.
这家伙真疯狂
This guy is crazy.
别开玩笑了
You got to be kidding me.
你换挡还是太早了
You're still upshifting early.
这样才能逼你刹车
I do that so you brake.
这样车尾就会打滑失控
You lose traction and the back end kicks out.
我注意到了
I noticed.
你知道我开车的习惯
Look, just because you know how I ride,
不代表你了解我本人
doesn't mean you know me.
那句话是怎么说的来着
You know what they say where we're from?
飙车给我看看  我会让你知道自己是谁
Show me how you drive, I'll show you who you are.
V8汽缸
V8.
你还是那么喜欢美国肌肉车
You never could resist American muscle.
伤疤挺漂亮
Nice scar.
你还是爱到处惹麻烦
You never could keep yourself out of trouble, either.
你还知道什么关于我的事儿
What else do you know about me?
关于你
About you?
我了解你的一切
Everything.
比如这条疤
Like this scar.
这是在咱俩第一次遇到那晚留下的
You got that the first night we met.
那时你才15岁
You were 15.
第一次参加绕圈赛
First street race.
有个想要出风头的小屁孩儿
Some kid trying to show off lost control of his car,
飙车失控了  车就在你身旁撞毁
wiped out right next to you.
没卸下你一条胳膊已经是万幸了
You're lucky you didn't lose your arm.
我猜猜
And let me guess,
是你救了我
you saved me.
不
No.
我就是那个想出风头的小屁孩儿
I was the kid showing off.
还有这里
And here...
博伊尔高地
Boyle Heights.
你在和我妹妹飙车
You were fleeing with my little sister Mia
被她逼得手忙脚乱
and got trapped in a corner.
你觉得飙着你的福特眼镜蛇
And you thought it was a good idea
穿墙而过是个绝佳的主意
to ride your Torino Cobra through a retaining wall.
好吧  那这条呢
All right, how about this one?
这是我们最后一次在一起的时候弄的
That's the last time we were together.
在DR时
In the DR.
你说你想晚上游泳
You wanted to go for a night swim.
结果被暗礁划伤了
You cut yourself on the reef.
我一路跟着你游
I followed you.
所以也被划了一道一模一样的
I even got this scar to match.
我不知道你为什么会出现
Look, I don't know why you're here,
但你肯定病的不轻
but I really think you're over your head.
我是为你而来的
I'm here for you.
你记忆里的那个女孩儿
That girl you remember,
并不是我
it's not me.
我只相信刚才亲眼所见的
Not from what I just saw.
随你怎么想
Like it or not,
但你一点也没变
you're still the same girl.
之前我就知道
I saw it out there.
现在更是坚信不疑
I see it right now.
我得走了
I got to go.
这是你的
It belongs to you.
她走了
There she goes,
又一次离开了你
leaving you again.
真他妈的绝情
Bloody fickle, that one.
你想来血腥暴力的我奉陪
You want bloody? We could do bloody.
一个街头小混混
A street kid,
在洛杉矶东部卖唱片机白手起家
starts out stealing DVD players in East L.A.,
最后则在里约偷了一亿然后金盆洗手
ends up heisting $100 million in Rio.
还不错吧
Not bad, huh?
是个美满的故事
It's a good story, isn't it?
简直让人羡慕了
Almost inspiring.
我不明白的是
See, what I couldn't fathom is
为啥他不愿意和那个美貌的巴西小妞
why he's not relaxing on a beach somewhere
安心在某个世外桃源隐居终老
with that cute little Brazilian number.
却要和政府的鹰爪霍布斯共事
Instead, he's working with a two- bit government hack like Hobbs.
然后我发现了
And then I realized,
他有一个弱点
he has a weak spot.
每个人都有弱点
We all got a weak spot.
在我年轻时
You know, when I was young,
我堂弟常说
my brother always used to say,
每个人都有自己的代名词
"Every man has to have a code."
我的是
Mine?
缜密
Precision.
在任务完成之前整个团队
A team is nothing but pieces
不过是分工合作的部件罢了
you switch out until you get the job done.
高效
It's efficient.
而且实用
It works.
而你
But you?
你却对错误的信念忠贞不渝
You're loyal to a fault.
你的代名词和"家人"息息相关
Your code is about family.
在闲暇之余可能还不错
And that's great in the holidays,
但这也让我能轻松料到你的行动
but it makes you predictable.
而这就代表着你很脆弱
And in our line of work, predictable means vulnerable.
也就是说只要我想  随时都能打垮你
And that means I can reach out and break you whenever I want.
但至少我知道我最终为何而死
At least when I go, I'll know what it's for.
至少你还有个代名词
Well, at least you have a code.
大多数人都没有
Most men don't.
那我给你一个机会
So, I'm going to give you a chance.
带着你的团队走人吧
Take your crew and walk away.
这是唯一能保你整个家族周全的法子
That's the only way you're going to keep your family safe.
你弟没教过你别拿家人作威胁人的筹码吗
Your brother never told you never to threaten a man's family?
我承认是做了件傻事
It's a pretty stupid thing to do.
但我也开门见山地说吧
But I'll make it simple for you.
她和这事儿脱了干系后我才会罢休
I walk away when she walks away.
好吧
Well, then,
看来这个令人羡慕的故事要走到头了
it appears this inspiring tale has come to an end.
如果你真打算这么干的话
If that's the way it has to go.
让我猜猜
Let me guess...
是霍布斯吧
Hobbs.
放马过来  王八蛋
Come on, you son of a bitch.
政府的鹰爪
The "Two- bit government hack."
再会了  托雷多
See you around, Toretto.
我们会再见的
You can bet on it.
莱利  肖驱车从巴特西往东南方向逃走了
Riley, Shaw's leaving Battersea, heading southeast.
让泰吉去追踪他的车
Have Tej track him on his live feed. Go.
我在想
You know what would have happened
如果我没在你车里放跟踪器会怎样
if I didn't put that tracker in your car?
这个吗
This one?
这玩意儿让我离抓到肖又进了一步
You know, this just got me one step closer to Shaw.
不论如何  托雷多
For what it's worth, Toretto,
希望你也能早点实现你的目的
I hope it gets you closer to what you want, too.
这么做最好值得
This better have been worth it.
是值了
More than you'll ever know.
美女
Pretty.
能给我看看吗
May I?
我得问你个问题  拉蒂
I'm going to ask you a question, Letty,
请你三思之后再回答
and I want you to think very hard before you answer.
当我下令
When I give you the order
让你杀了托雷多时
to take Toretto out,
你脑海中的第一反应是什么
what will your first thought be?
你怎么不看着我的眼睛
Why don't you look me in the eye
然后告诉我你看到了什么
and you tell me what you see.
留着吧
Keep it.
快说说情况如何了
Tej, talk to me, what have we got?
现在是能追踪到肖了
We were able to track Shaw after he left you and Dom,
但他也学聪明了
but this guy's smart,
所以我们也只能追踪到那么远
so we could only track him so far.
他知道城里所有摄像头的盲区
He seems to know all the city's blind spots.
我们在这一带跟丢了他
See, we lost him somewhere in here,
所以他可能在这附近半英里的范围内
which means he could be anywhere within that half- a- mile radius.
只要我们排查一下通话记录和租房信息
Maybe if we cross- reference phone records, leases...
不  这就是肖的行事风格
No, this has got Shaw's name written all over it.
这一段岔路极多
We've got vantage points, multiple exits,
还有地铁  高速路和下水道
subways, highways and storm drains.
真伤脑筋啊
Bad- ass and brains.
你再说下去我只有下岗了
Woman, you keep that up, I'm going to be out of a job.
好吧  咱们去抓那个王八蛋
All right, let's go nail that son of a bitch.
他们早就走了
They're long gone.
这儿什么都没剩下
There's nothing here.
也不尽然
There's never nothing.
总会有些蛛丝马迹的
There's always something.
出发吧伙计们
Let's go, guys.
肖  全员就位  一切照计划进行
Shaw, everyone is in place. All things moving according to plan.
很好  让他们上
Good. Send him in.
霍布斯打来的
Yo, it's Hobbs.
有什么发现  帕克  给我些好消息吧
What have you got, Parker? Give me something good.
有  你在肖的地盘找到的涂料
Yeah, that paint you got from Shaw's place
是专门定制的
is highly specialized.
可以防止雷达侦测的涂料
Anti- thermal low- IR coating.
-军用涂料  -正是
- Military. - Exactly.
有一清单欧洲军事基地都在用这种涂料
We got a list of bases around Europe that use this paint type
还没有特定的颜色
and those specific colors.
那就通查一遍所有肖的军事目标
All right, let's cross- reference that with all of Shaw's military targets.
总会有吻合的
I guaran- damn- tee you one of them is gonna match.
搞定
Bingo.
是西班牙的一个北约军事基地
It's a NATO base in Spain.
那意味着肖去了别的国家
That puts Shaw in a different country.
这样他已经领先我们8个小时了
That means he's got an eight- hour lead on us.
所以我们现在就该动身了
We gotta move now.
泰吉  把数据传给我
Tej, give me that info.
莱利和我现在就去锁定那个基地的位置
Riley and I will go ahead and we're going to lock down the base.
我们得靠自己去保护那个装置了
We're going to protect that component personally.
托雷多  立即把你的人和车调过来
Toretto, I'll arrange transportation for you and your cars.
换上你的西班牙装备  咱们西班牙见
You brush up on your Spanish, boys. I'll see you en EspaГ±a.
北约基地  鲁斯塔尼恩  西班牙
你个狗娘养的  居然成功了
You son of a bitch! You made it!
-别来无恙啊  伙计  -真高兴见到你
- What up, man? - Good to see you.
我也是  这是要干什么去
Good to see you. So, what's going on here?
查出他们要袭击西班牙的一个军事基地
Figured out they're hitting an army base in Spain.
肖的手下夜里越过了边境
Border patrol ID'ed Shaw's men crossing through last night.
霍布斯和莱利先去警告对方了
Hobbs and Riley went to lock down the base.
-我们在那边汇合  -唐在哪里
- They're going to meet us there. - Where's Dom?
你没回来他不愿意走
He wasn't going without you.
我查清楚拉蒂身上到底发生了什么了
I found out what happened to Letty.
都怪我
It's all my fault.
布莱恩
Brian,
不论你查到了什么
whatever you found out,
都只是为你自己而查
that's for you.
而我们现在要做的
What we're about to do now
是要让她回来
is for her.
我们设置了四支小队警戒巡逻
We've got four teams on overwatch,
目标周围的制高点也安插了狙击手
sniper- spotters in roosts north and south of the target.
把你的人都调开
Just keep all your men out of sight.
他们开着卡车冲进来时
When they drive that truck in here,
圣经中坚不可摧的城池 后崩毁
我希望能像推倒耶利哥之墙那样碾碎他们
I want to come crashing down on them like the walls of Jericho.
霍布斯
Hobbs,
这家伙想关闭保卫系统
I just caught this one disabling the perimeter security system.
你的基地已经不安全了
Your house is compromised.
有什么建议
What are you suggesting?
我不是在提建议
I ain't suggesting.
按着计划来  我们把目标转移出去
We follow protocol, we move the component out.
肖以为东西在这儿
Shaw thinks it's here.
我们要在肖到这儿前把目标转移走
We're going to get it out of here before he arrives.
我们最需要的就是隐蔽和快速
Stealth and speed are going to be our two best friends.
先把鸡蛋从鸡窝里拿出去
We're going to protect our little egg, move it out of the henhouse,
再等着那狡猾的老狐狸自投罗网
then we're going to wait for that goddamn fox to arrive.
他们在基地里抓住了一个肖的手下
I just got word they caught one of Shaw's men at the base.
是时候了
It's time.
感觉不大对劲
Something is not right.
他故意让我们发现那个人
He wanted us to find that guy.
还记得在国际刑警总部  你们对上他了
Think about it. At Interpol, you were face- to- face with him.
布莱恩  那你说怎么办
Brian, so what are you saying?
布拉加说找到肖的唯一途径就是等他来找你
Braga said the only way you get near Shaw is if he wants you to.
泰吉  装置现在在哪儿
Tej, where's that component?
正被运往一处安全的地方
They're moving it to a secure location.
肖的目的不是要袭击那个基地
Shaw ain't hitting that base.
他是想引出运输车队中途拦截
He's hitting the convoy.
行动
Let's go!
报告说运输车队受到攻击
We've got a report, the convoy's under attack.
上直升机  快
Get a chopper, now!
你们最好快点  他们已经控制了车队
Fellas, you better hurry up. They just took the convoy.
对了  唐
And Dom,
拉蒂也来了
Letty's with them.
一切照计划实施
We stick to the plan.
大家听好了
All right, you heard the man.
咱们要干净利落地解决这事
Let's play this fast and clean.
目标正前往你们所在的路上
That thing's heading your way.
所有系统就绪
All systems go.
一切就绪
Everything looks stable.
伙计们  我们得另想一个计划了
Uh, guys, we gotta come up with another plan.
他们整了辆坦克
They got a tank.
抱歉  刚才是有人说什么"坦克"吗
I'm sorry, did somebody just say "A tank"?
咱们有伴儿了
We got company, guys.
托雷多冲你来了
Toretto is coming right at you.
准备好武器
Okay. Get the weapons hot.
把卫星影像传输给我
Give me satellite imaging.
就在正前方
Straight ahead of us.
就是你了
There you are.
谁有B计划
Who's got a plan B?
B计划吗  B计划哪够
Plan B? Plan B?
我们还需要C计划  D计划  E计划
We need a plan C, D, E.
字母表都不够用了
We need more alphabets!
听着  我们尽力吧
Hey, we do what we do best.
随机应变行了吧
We improvise, all right?
约翰  去另一边车道
Okay, Jah. Take it to the other side.
我们来玩点儿刺激的
Let's have some fun.
你他妈的是不是有病  这不在计划里
What the hell is wrong with you? This isn't part of the plan.
把他们的注意力从无辜的人身上引开
Take their attention away from the people!
肖  你没必要做的这么绝
Shaw, you don't have to do this.
我们前面有个送上门来的
We got one right in front of us.
真他妈见鬼
Oh, shit!
你可真是狗屎运
You lucky bastard.
罗姆  挺住啊
Roman, you hang in there.
坚持住  伙计
Hang in there, man!
你们谁来做点什么  有辆坦克咬我屁股
Somebody better do something! I got a tank on my ass!
前面有个缺口
There's gotta be a break up ahead.
看啊
Oh, look,
有个桥
a bridge.
管他娘的
Screw it.
我们后面拖着辆车
We're dragging a car behind us.
布莱恩  我们必须得去给他们点儿回报
Brian, that Mustang would make a nice anchor.
我这就去
Yeah, I'm on it.
他妈的
Damn!
肖  我们得摆脱后面那辆车
Shaw, we've got to get rid of that car.
拉蒂  你来解决那难缠的缆线
Letty, go take care of the cable.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
该死
Shit!
现在轮到你了  托雷多
Okay, Toretto.
你的女人在这儿
Here's your girl...
来个幸福结局吧
And your happy ending.
拉蒂
Letty!
我的老天啊
Jesus Christ.
难以置信他们偷了辆70吨的坦克
I can't believe they stole a 70- ton tank
只为了得到三盎司电脑芯片
for a three- ounce computer chip.
那三盎司电脑芯片
That 3- ounce computer chip
比坦克要致命上千倍
is more deadly than 1,000 of those tanks.
那她呢
What about her?
她没问题
Not her.
她为肖卖命
She was working with Shaw.
已经过去了
Was,
她一直是我们中的一员
but she's always been one of us.
给他们点时间
Let's give them a minute.
得对付肖的同伙们了
Let's go process Shaw and his crew.
要写的报告
I've never looked more
这辈子都写不完了
forward to filling out paperwork in my life.
我不知道该怎么跟你说
Look, I don't even know how to say this to you,
但这一切都因我而起
but everything that's happened here is because of me.
都怪我你才落到如此境地
I'm the one that put you undercover...
别这么说
Stop.
我虽然之前的事都不记得了
I may not remember anything,
但是我确定我自己的一点
but I know one thing about myself.
那就是没有人能强迫我做我不想做的事
Nobody makes me do anything I don't want to.
这之后的下一段冒险你想去哪儿
So, what's our next adventure after this?
我们一起度过如何
How about we stay in one place?
你想去哪儿
Where are you thinking?
东京
Tokyo.
我们总是聊到东京
We always talk about Tokyo.
就去东京吧
Tokyo it is.
我能问你点事吗
Can I ask you something?
你怎么会知道
How did you know that
那有辆车会接住我们
there would be a car there to break our fall?
我不知道
I didn't.
有时你只需依靠信念
Some things you just have to take on faith.
托雷多
Hey, Toretto!
你来听一下
You need to hear this.
你们不会真以为你们赢了吧
You guys really think you've won.
就是你们崇尚的忠诚
This code you live by,
让你们到现在都搞不清状况
it's the very reason why you weren't even in the game.
我跟你说过我会做什么
I told you exactly what I was gonna do
如果你不退出  托雷多
if you didn't walk away, Toretto.
快走
Go!
但是你不听
But you didn't listen.
我说过我随时能摧毁你们
I told you I can reach out and break you whenever I want.
而且我已经做到了
And I have.
快下来
Come on.
-不  快走  -不
- Go. - No!
也许你该给米娅打个电话
Maybe you should call Mia.
-米娅  -布莱恩
- Mia? - Brian!
放开我
Let me go!
这笔交易算是成交了吧
So, this is how it's gonna go down.
乖乖帮我把手铐解开
You're gonna cut me loose from these cuffs,
把芯片交给我
you're gonna hand me the chip,
放我安全出去  不许跟踪我
I'm gonna walk out of here and you're not gonna follow.
你开什么玩笑
You must be joking.
看看他的表情
Look at his face.
问问他我是不是在开玩笑
Ask him if I'm joking.
一名人质的安危无法和百万市民匹敌
One hostage does not outweigh the threat to millions.
抱歉  这对我来说没影响
I'm sorry, but this changes nothing.
可是对我们有
It changes everything.
你命令你的人退下
You tell your men to stand down.
退下
Stand down.
托雷多
Toretto,
我需要你明白
I need you to know,
我们让他带着芯片出了那扇门的一刻
the moment we let him walk out that door with that chip,
"撤销""赦免"什么的
words like "Amnesty" And "Pardon"
可就都没了
walk out with him.
我们生来就跟这个没缘分
Those words went out the day we were born.
走吧  宝贝儿
Coming, babe?
当然
Of course.
我可不想错过这个
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
像我刚刚说的
Like I said,
你永远赢不了这场游戏
you were never in the game.
很快我们还会见面的
If I see you on the horizon,
我会打电话叫他们别弄死那女的
I'll make the call and the girl's dead.
托雷多的妹妹怎么办
So, what about Toretto's sister?
留着她没用了
There's no need for her anymore.
我刚刚把这片区域发出的信号都锁定了
I just jammed every signal up and down the spectrum.
我们出发
Let's move.
我和你们一起去
I'm coming with you.
这家伙到底想往哪里跑
Where the hell does this dude think he's going?
他被困在这个军事基地了
We're on an army base, he's trapped.
你个乌鸦嘴能闭上吗
Wow, you just had to open your mouth.
现在我们有个大飞机要对付
Now we got a big- ass plane to deal with.
不只是架飞机  简直是个星球
That ain't a plane. That's a planet.
打开货舱门
如果肖上飞机逃了你妹妹就死定了
She's as good as dead if Shaw gets away on that plane.
我们不会让他逃走的
Then we don't let him get away.
我们现在就搞定他们
Let's end this thing.
不飙宁死
Ride or die.
让他们起飞
Tell them to take off!
起飞  起飞
已经超载了  我们要提速
宝贝  送我到机翼下面
Babe, get me under the wing.
如果我能击中副翼  就能阻止它起飞
If I can hit that flap, we can keep it from taking off.
你小心点
You be careful.
这就是我们的工作
This is who we are.
该死
Shit!
外面发生什么事了
握紧方向盘
Grab the wheel!
唐
Dom!
走啊
Go!
快走
Come on. Let's go.
先进车里
Get in the car.
够起飞速度了
那就起飞吧
发生什么事了  你击中了飞机
What happened? Did you hit the flap?
你最好系好安全带
You should buckle up right now.
啥
What?
站错队了  婊子
Wrong team, bitch.
该死
Shit.
我抓住你了
I got you.
他们击中了副翼
他们要把我们拖垮了
抬高  抬高
泰吉
Tej!
保持这个速度
Keep her steady!
-快走  飞机要坠毁了  -走
- We gotta move, it's going down! - Go!
走  现在
Go, now!
快跳  快跳
Come on, let's move, move, move!
跳呀
Come on!
唐
Dom!
吉赛尔呢
Where's Gisele?
吉赛尔去哪儿了
就是这东西值十几亿
So this is worth billions, huh?
没错  就是它
Yes, it is.
开个价吧  唐
Name your price, Dom.
1327.
这次别烧焦了
Don't burn it this time. Please?
我什么时候烧焦过
I never go and burn it, man.
有好吃的
Good food.
空气质量不好  交通状况也很差
The air quality here is lousy, the traffic is bad,
但我觉得你会喜欢这地方
but I think you'll learn to like this place.
你都有自己的车库了
Yeah, and here you've got your own garage
你可以和老爹一起改车了
so you can build a car with Daddy.
我们一起来改车吗
We'll be building a car?
第一辆车最好是道奇Charger  杰克
First car better be a Charger, Jack.
日产跑车
是天际才对
You mean Skyline.
我说过他是托雷多家的人
Like I said, he's a Toretto.
宝宝都凌乱了
You're confusing the kid.
米娅  你就这么由着他吗
Mia, you're gonna let him get away with this?
你真要这样吗
You're really going to do it?
去东京
Tokyo.
我还有事要处理
Yeah, it's just something I gotta do.
你是知道我们会支持你的  随叫随到
You know we got your back, whenever you need us.
米娅  快把婴儿润肤油藏起来
Hey, Mia, you better hide your baby oil.
开个玩笑
I'm just playing.
你最好藏起脸上那张大屁股
You better hide that big- ass forehead.
就是个玩笑
I was just joking, but whatever.
没那么好笑好吗
Definitely not that funny.
这是官方文件
It's official.
你们都被赦免了
You're all free.
有你替我效力也挺不错的
It wasn't half bad, having you work for me.
明明就是你在为我服务
We all know you were working for me, Hobbs.
各抒己见
Agree to disagree.
多谢啦
Thank you.
祝你好运
Good luck.
伊莲娜
Elena?
拉蒂
Letty.
这是有多尴尬啊
This is gonna be awkward.
不过太他妈性感了
But sexy as hell.
谢谢你为他  为我们
I wanted to thank you for everything you've done for him.
做的一切
For us.
你是个出色的女人
It takes an amazing woman.
他是个不错的男人
He's an amazing guy.
他的确是
Yeah, he is.
别让他再惹麻烦了
Try to keep him out of trouble, huh?
你知道那一定不可能
Now, you know that's not gonna happen.
我就知道
I know.
对警察来说不错了
Not bad for a cop.
我从来没想过我会信任一个罪犯
I never thought I'd trust a criminal.
后会有期
Until next time.
伊莲娜
Elena.
你知道你不必离开
You know you don't have to go.
不  这些都是你的家人
All this... This is your family.
是真实的你自己
It's who you are.
而这才是我的家
This is my family.
是真正的我自己
This is who I am.
开饭啦
All right, everybody, let's eat.
要帮忙吗
Want some help with that?
菜都上了  可以开饭了
It's all here, it's done.
过来  伙计  我们一起把这些消灭掉
Come on, man, let's get with it.
吃了第一口  由他来做祷告
First bite, he's got grace.
房屋守则
House rules, man. House rules.
这感觉熟悉吗
Any of this feel familiar to you?
不
No.
但有家的感觉
But it feels like home.
这样我已经很满足了
That's good enough for me.
快来吧  要开动了
All right, y'all. Come on, let's do this.
罗姆
Okay, Roman,
我们来祷告吧
bless our table.
主啊  谢谢你让我们朋友团聚
Father, thank you for the gathering of friends.
主啊  感谢我们所得的选择
Father, we give thanks for all the choices we've made,
因为那些成就了今天的我们
because that's what makes us who we are.
我们会永远珍惜一路上我们所痛失的爱人
Let us forever cherish the loved ones we've lost along the way.
谢谢小天使的降临
Thank you for the little angel,
为大家庭添加一名新成员
the newest addition to our family.
谢谢您吧拉蒂带回家
Thank you for bringing Letty home.
最重要的是  谢谢您赐予的跑车
And most of all, thank you for fast cars.
东京
路上车辆请注意
两辆车在和一辆RX-7飙车
赛车朝中央涩谷方向行驶
日本东京都的特别区
RX-7到达路口
多米尼克・托雷多
Dominic Toretto.
你不认识我
You don't know me,
你马上会认识了
You're about to.